PAIGE GUTHRIE

pg-g.github.io

ு github.com/pg-g

y pg_g

SUMMARY

Front end developer with 5 years of experience, including 2 years managing a corporate website. Main tools include HTML, CSS, and LESS, with a basic knowledge of Javascript, AngularJS, and PHP. Passionate about learning, communication, and a great product.

EXPERIENCE

2014-15

Creative Lead / Web Developer

Jive Communications

- Took ownership of and continued to design, develop, and manage company website (jive.com) built on Wordpress (html, css, php) with Bootstrap.
- Managed a team of 4 (designers, creatives, content creators).
- Managed and developed company brand, including visual and voice.
- Supervised and aided in creation of creative content including print collateral, website material, videos, social media strategy, blog content, tradeshow assets, etc.

2012-14

Multimedia Specialist

Jive Communications

- Redesigned and rebuilt company website.
- Maintained user-facing knowledgebase and wiki; created training materials (PDFs, charts, videos) for customer training.
- Created and designed collateral for marketing, website, company identity, internal use, etc.

2012

Organic Internet Marketer

SkyRocket Inc.

- Developed js-based web app for marketing campaign.
- Created content (wrote articles and created graphics) for companyowned and client blogs.

2010-11

Senior Software Instructor

Brigham Young University Office of IT

- Taught courses in HTML, CSS, Dreamweaver, InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Qualtrics, etc. to students, staff, and faculty.
- Developed curriculum for InDesign CS5 used in university-wide classes.
- Created quick reference training cards for about 10 programs.
- Instituted peer evaluations that influenced employee raises to increase office accountability and professionalism.
- Developed orientation and trained 7 new hires over the course of 6 months.
- Co-wrote and edited a manual on how to develop effective curriculum and training sessions.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript

AngularJS

LESS

PHP

Wordpress

Illustrator
InDesign
Photoshop
Premiere
Excel

PERSONAL SKILLS

Collaboration

Leadership

Organization

Project Management

Training

EDUCATION

DevMountain

Web Development 2015

Brigham Young University

BA Design & New Media 2007-2012